<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="category_beaches">BEACHES</string>
    <string name="category_amusmentparks">PARKS</string>
    <string name="category_religiousplaces"> RELIGIOUS</string>
    <string name="category_gardens">GARDENS</string>

    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="near_by_attractions">Nearby Attractions</string>
    <string name="activities_to_do">Activities to do</string>
    <string name="best_time_to_visit">Best time to visit</string>
    <string name="things_to_do">Things to do</string>
    <string name="timings">Timings</string>
    <string name="entry_fee">Entry fee</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>

    <string name="aksa_beach">AKSA BEACH</string>
    <string name="juhu_beach">JUHU BEACH</string>
    <string name="chowpatty_beach">CHOWPATTY BEACH</string>
    <string name="dadar_beach">DADAR BEACH</string>
    <string name="madh_beach">MADH BEACH</string>
    <string name="marve_beach">MARVE BEACH</string>

    <string name="hanging_garden">HANGING GARDEN</string>
    <string name="kamla_nehru_park">KAMLA NEHRU PARK</string>
    <string name="jija_mata_udyan">JIJA MATA UDYAN</string>
    <string name="sgnp">SANJAY GANDHI NATIONAL PARK</string>

    <string name="essel_world">ESSEL WORLD</string>
    <string name="water_kingdom">WATER KINGDOM</string>
    <string name="adlabs_imagica">ADLABS IMAGICA</string>
    <string name="suraj_water_park">SURAJ WATER PARK</string>

    <string name="haji_ali">HAJI ALI</string>
    <string name="mahalaxmi_temple">MAHALAXMI TEMPLE</string>
    <string name="mount_mary_church">MOUNT MARY CHURCH</string>
    <string name="iskon_temple">ISKON TEMPLE</string>
    <string name="siddhivinayak_temple">SIDDHIVINAYAK TEMPLE</string>
    <string name="global_pagoda">GLOBAL PAGODA</string>
    <string name="elephanta_caves">ELEPHANTA CAVES</string>

    <string name="aksa_details">
        Aksa beach is one of those beaches in Mumbai with clean sand and less crowd.
        There are couple of vendors selling ice candies and some snacks.
        \n\nDue to its unsafe nature and distance in far suburb
        this beach is less explored by tourists.</string>
    <string name="aksa_nearby">
        Madh/Marve beach.
        \nEssel World and Water Kingdom.
        \nNational Park (Borivali).
        \nInorbit and Infinity malls at Malad Link road.</string>
    <string name="aksa_activities">
        Aksa has those sweet moments for people who want to spend sometime in peace and with nature but also within city.
        \n\nThe shades of coconut trees are blessing in summer, There are resorts near the beach which you can enjoy as well.
        The view of sunset is breath taking near the sea.
        \n\nAksa village has small huts which are converted to resturants and hotels, and one can relax and have snacks there.
    </string>
    <string name="aksa_best_time">
        The best time to visit Aksa beach is between the months September and April.
    </string>

    <string name="juhu_details">
        This beach is known to be one of the most visited beaches in India and is situated in Ville Parle in Western suburbs of Mumbai.
        \n\n Juhu beach is also famous amongst Indians for its street food and local delicacies.
        \n\nWatching the sunset in this wonderful place, guarded by the vast Arabian sea provides a beautiful visual for the eyes.
    </string>
    <string name="juhu_nearby">
        Versova is a nearby attraction from Juhu
    </string>
    <string name="juhu_activities">
        The Street foods such as "Bhel puri" ,"Pani puri" and "Pav Bhaji" are mouth watering delicacies one must try.
        \n\nOne can also taste cuisines from around the world as well as try local sea food near Juhu Beach.
        \n\nYoung  and adventerous ones can try activities like horse riding and camel rides.
    </string>
    <string name="juhu_best_time">
        The best time to visit Juhu beach is from months of October to February.
        \nIt is best to avoid visiting this beach during monsoon season because there can be possibilities of high tides.
    </string>

    <string name="chow_details">
        Dadar Chowpatty beach is a small and less crowded rocky beach with little sand around.
        People come here to enjoy silence,breeze,sunset view and the giant view of Bandra Worli sea Link Bridge.
        \n\nDadar beach is scenic with couple of attractions frequently visited by locals, walkable distance from shivaji park.
        \n\nAn awesome view of Bandra Worli sea Link accompanies you along with the sounds and breezes of the ocean
    </string>
    <string name="chow_nearby">
        Bandra Worli Sea Link.
        \nDadar Market,near station.
        \nYou can visit Siddhivinayak temple from there.
    </string>
    <string name="chow_activities">
        One can have view of Bandra worli sea link.
        \nIn north side of beach some refreshment can be found.
        \nWalkable distance to Shivaji park, where locals frequent.
    </string>
    <string name="chow_best_time">
        The best time to visit Dadar Chowpatty is between the months of September and April.
    </string>

    <string name="dadar_details">
        Dadar Chowpatty beach is a small and less crowded rocky beach with little sand around.
        People come here to enjoy silence,breeze,sunset view and the giant view of Bandra Worli sea Link Bridge.
        \n\nDadar beach is scenic with couple of attractions frequently visited by locals, walkable distance from shivaji park.
        \n\nAn awesome view of Bandra Worli sea Link accompanies you along with the sounds and breezes of the ocean
    </string>
    <string name="dadar_nearby">
        Bandra Worli Sea Link.
        \nDadar Market,near station.
        \nYou can visit Siddhivinayak temple from there.
    </string>
    <string name="dadar_activities">
        One can have view of Bandra worli sea link.
        \nIn north side of beach some refreshment can be found.
        \nWalkable distance to Shivaji park, where locals frequent.
    </string>
    <string name="dadar_best_time">
        he best time to visit Dadar Chowpatty is between the months of September and April.
    </string>

    <string name="madh_details">
        The beautiful beach is actually made of cluster of little villages and farmlands situated in the North western coast of Mumbai.
        \n\nThe shore is surrounded by mangroves which not only add to its scenic beauty,but also seperates the beach from the mainland.
        \n\nThe Madh Island beach attracts large crowds due to its calm waters and soothing scenery.
        \n\nThis beach is one of the cleanet one in the state.
    </string>
    <string name="madh_nearby">
        Madh Fort.
        \n\nErangal
        \n\nSt Bonaventuren
    </string>
    <string name="madh_activities">
        The Madh island beach is popular venue for shooting movies and Daily local soaps.
        It is a different experience to watch a live shoot.
        \n\n"The Retreat" and "The Resort" are the two popular five star hotels near the beach.Tourists can spend time
        enjoying the magnificent view along side the swimming pool of the resort and pamper themselves a little.
        \n\nThere is music being played on the beach for people to enjoy.
        \n\nPeople can explore local fishing communities that are situated close to the seashore.
    </string>
    <string name="madh_best_time">
        Best time to visit this beach is between October and June.At this time of the year there is less humidity
        and the weather is pleasend.
    </string>

    <string name="marv_details">
        Marve beach is located in the Western Suburbs of Malad in Mumbai.
        \n\nFerry Services to Essel World and Water kingdom theme parks and Manori are available from here.
        \n\nMarve beach can be reached from Malad railway station, Rickshaws and taxis.
        \n\nThe beach is not safe for swimming due to its sinking sand.
    </string>
    <string name="marv_nearby">
        Essel World theme park.
        Gorai Beach:The gorai beach is popular for its beautiful surroundings and villas.Ferries are available at Marve beach to gorai beach.
    </string>
    <string name="marv_activities">
        One will love to explore the sheer scenic beauty of these beaches in the absesnce of the chaotic crowd of vendors.
        \n\The beach has some very fine cottages built on the sea shore with a beautiful view of the arabian sea.
        \n\nThese cottages offer utmost luxury and hospitablity and luxury and are definetely tempting for most that see them.
    </string>
    <string name="marv_best_time">
        The Best time to visit this beach is from October to March, as there is less humidity.
        This beach is near from the residential area and ideal for a morning run or a morning walk.
    </string>


    <string name="essel_details">
        Essel World is the biggest and one of the first amusment parks in India.
        \n\nThis amusment park is popular for its colossal infrastructure and several exciting dry and wet rides.
        \n\nThe best feature of the Essel World Amusment park is that it is open all year round.
    </string>
    <string name="essel_attract">
        There are several high adrenaline fun rides catering to various age groups.
        Dry rides,Wet rides, a discotheque and a massive food court are some of the many attractions of this park.
        \n\nAmong all fun activities that can be enjoyed, the ice skating ring,discotheque and bowling alley serve as the prime attractions
        for people.
        \n\nThere are also avenues for shopping and food courts for people looking for a holistic experience.
    </string>
    <string name="essel_timings">
        11 am to 7 pm on Weekdays.
        \n10 am to 7 pm on Weekends.
    </string>
    <string name="essel_entry">
        390 Rupees to 490 Rupees for Children.
        \n590 Rupees to 790 Rupees for Adults.
        \n290 Rupees for Senior citizens.
    </string>
    <string name="essel_best_time">
        The best time to visit Essel World is from October to March.
    </string>

    <string name="king_details">
        Water Kingdom is known to be Asia\'s biggest water theme park and was established in 1998.
        \n\nLocated in Gorai,Mumbai,the water park is an extension of Essel World.
        \n\nApart from the slides ,rides and other fun activities, the water park also has a number of restaurants that promise
        tourists lip-smacking delights.
        \n\nWater Kingdom is truly a remarkable place that offers unlimited fun for all who visit the park.
    </string>
    <string name="king_attract">
        "Aquadrome" is a unique feature at the Water Kingdom,where a dance zone of 7000 square feet is set with numerous water sprinklers.
        \n\nTourists can enjoy dancing to the music while being occasionally sprayed with water from the sprinklers.
        \n\nThe "Misphisly Hill" has 12 terrifying high adrenaline rides that are extremely popular at the water park.
        \n\nThe "Drifting River" is a loop of gently flowing water that promises a ton of excitement with slow currents, where
        people can relax and float.
        \n\nSome of the other enthralling attractions here include the "juicy jammer","Turbi Terminator","Black Demon" and "Lemon Drops".
    </string>
    <string name="king_timings">
        11 am to 7 pm on Weekdays
        \n11 am to 7 pm on Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="king_entry">
        590 Rupees for Children.
        \n890 Rupees for Adults.
        \n290 Rupees for Senior citizens.
    </string>
    <string name="king_best_time">
        One can visit Water Kingdom throughout the year.
    </string>

    <string name="imagica_details">
        Adlabs Imagica is India\'s first and only International Standard Theme park offering fun, action, entertainment, dining, shopping
        at a single location.
        \n\nImagica is driven by whole world of fantastical themes to bring Indian families experiences that they have never had befrore
        \n\nIn every zone you will be immersed in a new theme that will extend through every touch point.
        \n\nWith 26 attractions and rides and 5 themed restaurants,Imagica is a place where stories come alive.
    </string>
    <string name="imagica_attract">
        Thrill Rides
        \nFamile Rides
        \nKiddie Rides
        \nThemed Attractions
    </string>
    <string name="imagica_timings">
        11 am to 8 pm on Weekdays
        \n11 am to 9 pm on Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="imagica_entry">
        <b>Weekdays</b>
        \n1200 Rupees for Children.
        \n1500 Rupees for Adults.
        \n1200 Rupees for Senior citizens.
        \n\n<b>Weekends and Holidays</b>
        \n1600 Rupees for Children.
        \n1900 Rupees for Adults.
        \n1600 Rupees for Senior citizens.
    </string>
    <string name="imagica_best_time">
        The theme park can be visited all year around.
    </string>

    <string name="suraj_details">
        Suraj water park is an exciting water recreation paradise guranteeing an enthralling adventure for all those who visit the park.
        \n\nOne can also find a massive figure of Lord Shiva with river ganga flowing from his mane.
        \n\nSuraj water park is indeed a perfect destination to relax and connect with nature.
        \n\nThe water park is a five time Limca Book of Record Holder and is a winner of international as well as national awards.
    </string>
    <string name="suraj_attract">
        "Nanha tal" is a little slide for children and offers a great deal of excitement.
        \n\nOther fascinating slides like "Ding Dong", "Lakbak and Zabak" and "Sing-a-Song" are star attractions of Suraj Water park.
        \n\nThe "Crazy River" and "Lazy River" are water areas that emulate the flow of real rivers, where children and adults are pulled
        by the current, using floats and rubber tubes as protection against the water.
    </string>
    <string name="suraj_timings">
        10 am to 6 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="suraj_entry">
        <b>Weekdays</b>
        \n500 Rupees for Children.
        \n650 Rupees for Adults.
        \n\n<b>Weekends</b>
        \n600 Rupees for Children.
        \n800 Rupees for Adults.
    </string>
    <string name="suraj_best_time">
        One can visit Suraj water park all year round.
    </string>


    <string name="haji_details">
        The Haji Ali Dargah is a historical landmarik in Mumbai, and is also one of the most prestigous Islamic symbols situated in
        South Mumbai.
        \n\nThe Haji Ali was built by a wealthy Muslim merchant who became a saint named Haji Ali Shah Bukhari.
        \n\nPeople from all over the world visit the Haji Ali Dargah irrespective of their case ,religion or creed.
        \n\nThe Haji Ali Dargah is popular pilgrimage site today and most of the tourist visit the tomb of Pir Haji Ali Shah
        Bukhari to seek blessings for Wealth,Health, marriage etc
        \n\nThe Haji Ali Dargah is made of "Makrana" marble that Emperor Shah Jahan used to build the Taj Mahal.
        \n\nThe Haji Ali Dargah houses two important monuments-tomb of Pir Haji Ali Bukhari and a mosque.
    </string>
    <string name="haji_timings">
        5.30 am to 10 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="haji_entry">
        No entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="haji_things">
        Apart from visiting the Dargah ,offering prayers and seeking blessings of the saint, there are various other things to do in and
        around the Dargah.
        \n\nLocal stalls outside the comples of Haji Ali Dargah will give you the opportunity to indulge in some delicous local cuisines
        and local specialities such as Kebabs, Chaat,Ice cream,Mughlai Biryani etc.
        \n\nIf you are an avid shopper the best places would be crawford market and fashion street.
        \n\nIf you enjoy serenity and happen to be a nature lover, you can decide to unwing at the beach at Mahim Bay.
    </string>
    <string name="haji_nearby">
        Worli Sea Link
        \nBreach Candy
        \nNana Chowk
        \nMahalakshmi Race Course stadium
    </string>

    <string name="maha_details">
        Mahalaxmi Temple is an ancient temple dedicated to honor "Godess Mahalaxmi" who is also known as the "Godess of Wealth".
        \n\nA large number of believers throng this temple on Fridays.
        \n\nDuring the days of Navratri\'s festival thousands of devotees flock this shrine to witness the celebrations.
        \n\nIdol of Godess Mahalaxmi is decorated elegantly with gold bangles,pearl necklaces,nose studs and flowers etc.
        \n\nOne can find the three idols of Godess Mahalaxmi ,Godess Mahakali and Godess Saraswati places inside the Mahalaxmi Temple.
    </string>
    <string name="maha_timings">
        6 am to 10 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="maha_entry">
        No entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="maha_things">
        One can visit the Mahalaxmi Temple during Navratri to witness the glorious destive celebrations.
        \n\nDevotees can offer coconuts,sweets,flowers etc to honor the Godess during this hold ocassion.
        \n\nOne can also shop here as there are plenty of stalls selling flowers,sweets and religious relics withing the temple complex.

    </string>
    <string name="maha_nearby">
        The Atria Mall located in Worli is very close to Mahalaxmi temple and is an amazing place to visit, especially if you love
        Shopping.
        \n\nThe Heera Panna Shopping Center is one of the most popular shopping areas in Mumbai and is sited close to the temple.
        \n\nOne can also visit the Haji Ali Dargah which is another popular tourist destination.
    </string>

    <string name="mount_details">
        Mount Mary Church is Roman Catholic Church, dedicated to Virgin Mary,situated in Mumbai.
        \n\nWhat makes this church more beautiful is that it is sited on top of a hill known as Sunderban Bandra
        which overlooks the mighty Arabian sea
        \n\nIt is believed that the church has unbelievable healing powers and for this reason, the church is herded by devotees
        every day.
        \n\nThe Bandra Fair or the "Feast of Mount Mary" is a week long celebration held every September at the Mound Mary church.
    </string>
    <string name="mount_timings">
        <b>Monday to Saturday</b>
        \n6 am to 1 pm
        \n2 pm to 8 pm
        \n\n<b>Sunday</b>
        \n6 am to 8 pm
    </string>
    <string name="mount_entry">
        No entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="mount_things">
        The week of the "Bandra Fair" or the "Feast of Mount Mary", which is held in September ,is a perfect time to visit Mount Mary Church
        as it is completely decorated.
        \n\nOne can shop for religous artifacts innovatively shaped candles,wax figures of virgin mary or even buy Goan sweets from
        various stalls outside the church.
        \n\nOne can get a spectacular view of sunsets from this church.
    </string>
    <string name="mount_nearby">
        "Father Agnel" is another church sited on Carter Road, close to Mount Mary Church.
        \n\nThe famous Jogger\'s park is also situated in Bandra and is a must visit for all tourists.
        \n\nYou can also explore Linking road, which is perfect flea market for shopping.
    </string>

    <string name="isk_details">
        International Society for Krishna Conciousness, also popularly known as the Hare Krishna movement is a spritual society founded
        by his Divine Grace A.C Bhaktivedanta Swami Prabhupada in July 1966 in New York.
        \n\nThis temple, also known as the "Hare Rama Hare Krishna temple" and "Radha Rasabihariji" is dedicated to Lord Krishna" and was built by the ISKON Foundation.
        \n\nThe temple is embellished with various paintings and statues within its interiors, making the temple look all the more mesmerizing.
        \n\nThe temple is an apt spot for meditation and prayers especially for the people who seek to increase ones spritiual knowledge and add on to their intellectual development.
        \n\nThe aim of ISKON is to acquiant all people of world with universal principles of self-realization and good conciousness so that they may derive the highest benefit of spritiual understanding ,unity and peace.
    </string>
    <string name="isk_timings">
        <b>"Darshans"(prayers) timings are as follows</b>
        \n\n4.30 am Mangala Aarti.
        \n5.30 am   Tulsi puja.
        \n7.15 am   Sringar darshan
        \n7.30 am   Guru puja
        \n8.00 am   Bhagavatam discourse
        \n0.30 pm   Raj Bhoga Aarti
        \n4.30 pm   Usthapana Aarti
        \n7.00 pm   Sahdhya Aarti
        \n7.30 pm   Bhagvad gita discourse
        \n8.30 pm   Shayana Aarti
        \n\n<b>Temple will be closed between</b>
        \n1.00 pm to 4.30 pm
        \n9.00 pm to 4.30 am
    </string>
    <string name="isk_entry">
        No entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="isk_things">
        Attend the various temple activities chant hymns and meditate.
        \n\nOne can witness and be part of the revelries,chanting the "Mahamantra" inside the temple.Apart from this the temple
        conducts prayers,"bhajans" every evening.
        \n\nParticipate in various spritual, cultural and learning activities. These activities are held within the temple and
        one can either observe or participate in those activities and get knowledge about the vedas.
        \n\nEnjoying celebrations and festive activities during "Janmashtami" which is an important day at ISKON temple.
    </string>
    <string name="isk_nearby">
        Juhu Beach is right next to the temple and is a perfect get away from the busy city life.
        \nChowpatty Beach
    </string>

    <string name="sid_details">
        Siddhivinayan Temple is a standing testament of beauty and architecture.
        \n\nThis ancient temple was constructed in 1801 and is dedicated to the elephant=head deity of Hinduism,"Lord Ganesh".
        \n\nTuesday is considered to be the most important day for "Puja" and "Darshan" at this temple.
        \n\nWhen one visits this place, one cannot help but admire the temple\'s ancient style of architecture and its many features.
        \n\nThe idol of Lord Ganesha is sculpted from a single black stone.
        \n\nAn elegant masterpiece with a unique design, the Siddhivinayak Temple is a hotspot for tourists who visit Mumbai.
    </string>
    <string name="sid_timings">
        5.30 am to 10 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="sid_entry">
        No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="sid_things">
        Phool Gali is a street filled with various stalls that leads towards Siddhivinayak Temple.
        \n\nThe shopkeepers on this street sell fresh flowers, sweets,coconuts and many other "puja" accessories which one can buy on their
        way to the temple for offering to the lord.
        \n\nAs Tuesday is considered to be a special day for Lord Ganesh devotees,"Aartis" are performed inside the temple which is flocked
        by devout worshippers.
        \n\nDuring "Sankashti Chaturthi" and "Angaraki" , a large number of devotees gather to attend the special events held within
        this temple.
    </string>
    <string name="sid_nearby">
        Worli sea Link
        \nShivaji Park
    </string>

    <string name="pag_details">
        The magnificent golden Global Pagoda is the highlight at one of the Top 5 Vipassana Meditation centers in India.
        \n\nIts the world\'s largest stone dome built without any supporting pillars.
        \n\nThe dome is approximately 29 meters high, twice the size of previously largest monument of its kind in Bijapur,India.
        \n\nThere\'s also an art gallery showing the life and teachings of lord Buddha.
    </string>
    <string name="pag_timings">
        9 am to 7 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="pag_entry">
        No entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="pag_things">
        One can visit Painting Gallery which depicts stories of people benefitted from Vipassana practive in Buddhas time.
        \n\nVisit the Buddha Statue to honor Buddha as a great spritual scientish who taught Vipassana and nature based
        teachings for benefit of Humanity.
        \n\nOne can also visit the food court for refreshment needs and visitors and Burmese Murals for Culture and art
        enthusiast to learn about Burmese customs.
    </string>
    <string name="pag_nearby">
        Essel World
        \nGorai Beach
    </string>

    <string name="ele_details">
        Elephanta caves lie just off the coast of the Arabian Sea, situated at a 10 km radius from the bustling metropolis.
        \n\nElephanta Caves are perfect expression of archaic indian art associated to the cult of Lord Shiva.
        \n\nThe island on which the caves are built was originally known as Gharapuri, and the Portugese retitled it as ELphanta
        Island when they discovered a large stone structure of an elephant on the Island.
        \n\nThe temple was primarily built for the worship of Lord Shiva and "Shivaism".
        \n\nThe Elephanta island is a quiet and picturesque island with green foilage and harmless primates scanpering about.
    </string>
    <string name="ele_timings">
        9 am to 5 pm Tuesday to Sunday
        \n Monday closed

    </string>
    <string name="ele_entry">
        10 Rupees per person (Indian)
        \n250 Rupees per person (Non Indian)
    </string>
    <string name="ele_things">
        A paradise for women, this little market offers sculptures made of marble, jewellery, clothes ,paintings and many
        other local arts and wood work.
        \n\nIf you are interested in locan indian Food, an MTDC run resort offers a find spread at a reasonable cost.
        \n\nOne can also enjoy the scenic beauty of this Island.
    </string>
    <string name="ele_nearby">
        Gateway of India
    </string>


    <string name="hang_details">
        The Hanging Gardens id dedicated to its barrister Pherozesha Mehta,which is why these gardens are also known as pherozesha
        Mehta Garden.
        \n\nThis reknowned garden located on the Malbar Hill is known for its splendig green vegetation and animal shaped hedges, which
        is an interesting sight for anyone who visits this spot.
        \n\nAdding to the garden\'s beauty is the comforting view of the vash Arabian sea.
        \n\nWatching the sunset from the Hanging gardens would provide you with an experience worth remembering.
        \n\nThe striking flower, clock situated in the center of the garden, serves as the main attraction for all tourists.
    </string>
    <string name="hang_things">
        One can spend an entire day exploring the natural beauty of these terraced gardens.
        \n\nYou can also watch a glorious sunset from these gardens.
        \n\nIf photography is your hobby,then Hanging gardens is the best place for you to make use of your creative
        photography skills.
        \n\nHanging Gardent is the perfect place for early morning jogs and yoga.
    </string>
    <string name="hang_timings">
        5 am to 9 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="hang_entry">
        No entry fee
    </string>
    <string name="hang_best_time">
        Its open throughout the year, and can be visited anytime of the year
    </string>

    <string name="kamla_details">
        Situated on top of the Mumbai\'s Malbar Hill, this park is named after Jawarlal Nehru\'s wife, Kamala Nehru.
        \n\nFrom this garden, one can enjoy the spectacular sight of the Chowpatty Beach and also Marine Drive(Queen\'s Necklace)/
        \n\nKamala Nehru Park is a show shaped structure ,with widespread lush greenery.
    </string>
    <string name="kamla_things">
        People come here to enjoy the lovely view of the Girgaum Chowpatty beach which is quite close to Kamala Nehru Park.
        \n\One can also enjoy the panoramic views of marine drive from the park particularly at sunset.
        \n\nSituated atop a hill, this park attracts beautiful birds during monsoon.
        \n\nKamala Nehru Park is famous for a unique structure called the Old Women\'s shoe or Boot House, that famously is fun
        for kids.
    </string>
    <string name="kamla_timings">
        5 am to 9 pm Weekdays and Weekends
    </string>
    <string name="kamla_entry">
        No entry fee
    </string>
    <string name="kamla_best_time">
        Open throughout the year and can be visited any time.
    </string>

    <string name="jija_details">
        Jijamata Udyan formerly called as "Ranichi Bagh" after the orignal British name Victoria Gardens, and now
        also known as Veermata Jijabai Bhonsle Udyan,is a zoo and garden located at Byculla, in the heart of Mumbai, India.
        \n\nJijamata udyan is full of lush green trees and famous for the species of birds and animals easily seen once
        you enter Jijamata udyan.
        \n\nWith the green trees is a botanical garden in the pathway inside the zoo flower plants, herb plants and other new species
        of plants.
    </string>
    <string name="jija_things">
        One can visit the different gardens inside the zoo like zoo botanical garden, Tactile garden, Medicinal Garden.
        \n\nPeople can see various animalsa around them.
    </string>
    <string name="jija_timings">
        9 am to 6 pm Thursday to Tuesday
        \n Closed on Wednesday
    </string>
    <string name="jija_entry">
         5 Rupees for Adults.
        \n2 Rupees for Children.
    </string>
    <string name="jija_best_time">
        The park is open throughout the year and can be visited anyime except on wednesdays.
    </string>

    <string name="sgnp_details">
        The park enthralls its visitors with its mesmerizing fauna and flora
        \n\nThe presence of 2400 year old Kanheri caves carved out from rock cliffs,in its premises is another added attraction
        of this place.
        \n\nThe gorgeous sight of the lakes, rivers,valleys and hills provide an in-depth theraputic effect on body and mind.
    </string>
    <string name="sgnp_things">
        Every visitor who comes here enjoys the great panorama of the lush greenery with a ramarkable collection of
        birds,butterflies and various kinds of fauna including the wild leopard.
        \n\nOne would find a varied collection of wild animals including Bonnet and Rhesus monkeys, Indian Hare, Sambar deer,
        Gray Lungur, Chital, Macaque and many more.
        \n\nAnother major attractions of this place is presence of Atlas Moth, world\'s largest moth.Karvi an exotic variety of flora
        is also found here which blossoms only once in eight years.
        \n\nAuthorities of the park also arranged tiger and lion safari which attracts about 2 million tourists every year.
        \n\nThe thich cover of the dense forest is home to different types of plants and trees including khair, kusum ,teak, bamboo
        and many others.
    </string>
    <string name="sgnp_timings">
        7 am to 6.30 pm Tuesday to Sunday
        \nClosed on Monday
    </string>
    <string name="sgnp_entry">
        <b>Entry Fees</b>
        \n33 Rupees per Adult.
        \n\n<b>Boat rides</b>
        \nBoating timings 9.30 am to 5.30 pm
        \n33 Rupees per person for 2 seater boat.
        \n66 Rupees per person for 4 seater boat.
        \n\n<b>Lion and Tiger Safari</b>
        \nSafari timings 9 am to 12.30 pm
        \nand 2 pm to 4.30 pm
        \n55 Rupees for Adult.
        \n22 Rupees for Child.
        \n\n<b>Kanheri Caves</b>
        \nKanheri caves timings 9 am to 5 pm
        \nRupees 5 for Adult.

    </string>
    <string name="sgnp_best_time">
        The National park can be visited any time of the year.
    </string>


</resources>
